Draft protective patch for the S75.
This configuration (at the time laid out on the SVN)
calculated at the 47-th version of the firmware.
; SecPatch - actually a patch in the folder Release \ Exe are script, *. vkp
; SecCaller - simple elf, causing the body of the patch for debugging purposes.
; IMSIReader - elf to read the current IMSI, IMSI saves in the file 0: \ Misc \ IMSI.txt

In the folder Utils must set PF to create a *. vkp